export const decks = {
  hgdfasaa: {
    id: 'hgdfasaa',
    category: 'Niemiecki',
    title: 'Wyposażenie domu',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'łóżko',
        answer: 'das Bett',
      },
      {
        question: 'obraz',
        answer: 'das Bild',
      },
      {
        question: 'komputer',
        answer: 'der Computer',
      },
      {
        question: 'okno',
        answer: 'das Fenster',
      },
      {
        question: 'globus',
        answer: 'der Globus',
      },
      {
        question: 'telewizor',
        answer: 'der Fernseher',
      },
      {
        question: 'hamak',
        answer: 'die Hӓngematte',
      },
      {
        question: 'grzejnik',
        answer: 'der Heizung',
      },
      {
        question: 'wysokie łóżko',
        answer: 'das Hochbett',
      },
      {
        question: 'hoker/taboret',
        answer: 'der Hocker',
      },
      {
        question: 'komoda',
        answer: 'die Kommode',
      },
      {
        question: 'lampa',
        answer: 'die Lampe',
      },
      {
        question: 'szafka nocna',
        answer: 'die Nachtkӓstchen',
      },
      {
        question: 'kosz na papier',
        answer: 'der Papierkorb',
      },
      {
        question: 'pluszak',
        answer: 'das Plüschtier',
      },
      {
        question: 'plakat',
        answer: 'das Poster',
      },
      {
        question: 'regał',
        answer: 'das Regal',
      },
      {
        question: 'szafa',
        answer: 'der Schrank',
      },
      {
        question: 'biurko',
        answer: 'der Schreibtisch',
      },
      {
        question: 'fotel',
        answer: 'der Sessel',
      },
      {
        question: 'pufa',
        answer: 'der Sitzsack',
      },
      {
        question: 'kanapa/sofa',
        answer: 'das Sofa',
      },
      {
        question: 'lustro',
        answer: 'der Spiegel',
      },
      {
        question: 'krzesło',
        answer: 'der Stuhl',
      },
      {
        question: 'dywan',
        answer: 'der Teppich',
      },
      {
        question: 'stoł',
        answer: 'der Tisch',
      },
      {
        question: 'waza/dzbanek',
        answer: 'die Vase',
      },
      {
        question: 'zasłona',
        answer: 'der Vorhang',
      },
      {
        question: 'zegar ścienny',
        answer: 'die Wanduhr',
      },
      {
        question: 'budzik',
        answer: 'der Wacker',
      },
      {
        question: 'kwiatek w doniczce',
        answer: 'die Zimmerpflanze',
      },
    ],
  },
};
